英文字幕从www.AllSubs.org下载
新浪微博@蓝色风暴911 原创翻译
Yes, sir. I will do that.
是的，先生。我会去做！
Urgent. Urgent.
紧急。紧急。
Where's Lin? Lin Braddock?
林在哪里？林・巴洛克？
She left.
她离开了。
You know where she went?
你知道她去哪儿了吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Lin...
林...
is your man really take you to America?
你的男人真的会带你去美国吗？
Yes, of course.
是的，当然。
What about all this?
这些怎么办？
I can't take everything.
我不能带上所有东西。
What about this?
这个呢？
Yes. Take it.
是的，带上。
Take anything you want.
带上任何你想要的东西。
Stay back! Stay back!
退后！退后！
I can't let you in!
我不能让你进去！
Please disperse.
请散开。
We can't help you all.
我们不能帮助你们所有人。
We have no room!
我们没有房间！
Captain, has a Lin Braddock
come through the gate?
队长，有没有一个叫林・巴洛克的人通过大门？
If you work for the Embassy,
have your papers ready!
如果你为大使馆工作，准备好你的证件！
Not yet, Colonel.
没有，上校。
You're a friend of Lin?
你是林的一个朋友？
I'm her husband.
我是她的丈夫。
She went to her home.
她去自己家了。
When?
什么时候？
One hour, maybe two.
一个小时前，也许两个。
She had to get her papers.
她必须拿到自己的证件。
Please disperse!
请散开！
The dress is so beautiful.
这件礼服真漂亮。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Good-bye, Min. Take care.
再见，敏。保重。
Bye.
再见。
Hold it.
且慢。
We found her upstairs.You know her?
我们在楼上找到她。你认识她？
Guess what I've got.
猜猜我得到了什么。
All right. Hit it.
好吧。炸了它。
Roger.
明白。
【全称：I have received all the last message。
其中R是RECEIVE，O是ALL，GER就是MESSAGE，
这个词是由WW2(二战)的时候开始使用的。】
I said get the hell off of there!
我说过离开那个鬼地方！
I'm Lin Braddock!
我是林・巴洛克！
Look at the list!
看看这个表格！
I work for the Embassy!
我为大使馆工作！
Lin Braddock!
林・巴洛克！
Captain!
队长！
What is it?
什么事？
She says she's on the list.
她说她在表格上。
What name?
什么名字？
Lin Braddock!
林・巴洛克！
I'm a translator for the embassy!
我是一名大使馆的翻译！
Give me your papers.
把你的证件给我。
I lost them!They stole it!
我把它们弄丢了！他们偷走了！
Please! Look at the list!
拜托了！看看这个表格！
I need your papers!
我需要你的证件！
I told you! Somebody stole them!
我刚告诉过你，有人把证件偷走了！
Oh, God! You have to believe me!
哦，上帝!你必须相信我！
Well, there's nothing I can do about that.
额，那我没有办法。
Please! Lin! Look at the list!
拜托了！林！看看这个表格！
This morning there was a Colonel Braddock.
今天早上那里是有一个巴洛克上校。
Is Colonel Braddock your husband?
巴洛克上校是你的丈夫？
Yes! Yes!
是的！是的！
For crying out loud! These people are crazy!
搞什么名堂！这些人都疯了！
Get them down!
把他们放倒！
Shoot them! Get it together!
向他们射击！都集中起来！
Grab the seal.
抓住标志。
Step aside! Move!
让开！走开！
Come on, Junior.Get these folks out!
加油，晚辈。把这些人赶出去！
Get off me!Get out of the way!
离开我！把路让开！
Move! Stand aside!
走开！靠边站！
Let's go!
我们走！
Please!
拜托！
Wait! Please!
等等！拜托！
Please!
拜托！
Commander, please.
指挥官，拜托。
I give you a thousand dollar.
我给你一千美元。
Please. I love America.Come on.
拜托。我热爱美国。来吧。
Hey.
嘿。
Let me go up.
让我上去。
Let me go!
让我走！
OK. Take off.
好吧。起飞。
Son of a bitch!
婊子养的！【王八蛋】
Don't worry.We got you, Colonel!
别担心。我们抓住你了，上校！
That bastard was probably V.C.
那杂种可能是副主席。
All right.There you go, Colonel.
好吧。就这样，上校。
All right.Move them out. Move!
好了。快把他们运出去。快走！
No medals, no ribbons
没有奖牌，没有丝带
No welcome parade
没有欢迎游行
It's a lonely road home
这是一条孤独的回家路
And a heavy price to pay
和一个沉重的代价
Now I say a prayer
现在我做一次祈祷
For those that remain
为了那些留在这里的人
And I wonder
并且我怀疑
Will they ever find freedom again?
他们还会再一次找到自由吗？
- Hi, Cindy. - Hey.
- 嗨，辛迪。- 嘿。
I should run for president.
我要竞选总统。
What'd you say?
你刚说什么？
I didn't think he needed to.
我不认为他需要。
Oh, really?
哦，真的？
Mr. Braddock?
巴洛克先生？
That's right.
正是。
Colonel James Braddock?
詹姆斯・巴洛克上校？
What can I do for you?
我能为你做些什么？
Could I have a few moments of your time?
我可以打扰你一些时间吗？
- Sit down.- Thank you.
- 请坐。- 谢谢。
Please, uh...
拜托，额...
could we please talk more privately?
我们可以更加私密的交谈吗？
Yeah. Sure.
是的。当然。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Would you like something to drink?
你需要喝点什么吗？
No, no. Thank you.
不，不需要。谢谢。
I am Reverend Polanski...
我是波兰斯基牧师...
from the Amerasian Children's
Mission in Vietnam.
来自越南的美亚混血儿童教会。【慈善机构】
Occasionally,
I come to this country...
偶尔，我回到这个国家...
to raise funds for the mission.
为了教会筹集资金。
I was hoping I could find you before I went back.
我一直希望能在回去之前找到你。
Find me? Why?
找到我？为什么？
About a year ago,
a young Amerasian child...
大约一年之前,一个年幼的美亚混血儿童...
came to the mission
begging for help.
来到教会乞求帮助。
He told me that his mother was sick.
他告诉我说他的妈妈生病了。
I went to see if there was anything I could do...
我过去探望有什么事情自己可以帮忙...
and found out she worked for the U.S. Embassy...
并且发现她曾经为美国大使馆工作...
during the war.
是在越战期间。
She has been severely punished by the Vietnamese government.
她已经被越南政府严厉地惩罚。
Having the half-American son has made things...
有一个半美国血统的儿子让事情变得...
even worse for her.
对她而言更加糟糕。
I'm sorry to hear that, but...
听到这些我很伤心，但是...
what's that got to do with me?
那和我有什么关系？
The woman's married name is Mrs. James Braddock.
这位女士的已婚名字是詹姆斯・巴洛克夫人。
What did you say?
你说什么？
I'm talking about your wife, Mr. Braddock.
我正在谈论你的妻子，巴洛克先生。
Lin Tan Cang.
林昙苍。
You're mistaken.
你搞错了。
No. There is no mistake.
不，没有搞错。
My wife died during the fall of Saigon.
我的妻子在西贡沦陷时牺牲了。
Your wife is alive.I know her quite well.
你的妻子还活着。我知道她很好。
Your son's name is Van.
你儿子的名字叫凡。
He's now 12 years old.
他现在12岁。
My wife and I didn't have a son.
我的妻子和我没有生下儿子。
Why is it so hard for you to believe me?
为什么对你来说相信我是如此的艰难？
Because I saw my wife's body burned to a crisp, that's why.
因为我看到自己妻子的尸体都烧焦了，这就是原因。
You may have seen a body...
你可能看到过一具尸体...
but it wasn't your wife.
但那不是你的妻子。
Lin Tan Cang is alive!
林昙苍还活着！
Believe whatever you want, Reverend.
坚信你所想要的一切，牧师。
I know better.
我很清楚。
Your few moments are up.
给你的一些时间结束了。
Oh, they had this great
place in Georgetown.
哦，他们在乔治敦有这个伟大的地方。
Really nice.
真的不错。
Yeah, of course.
I saw it last week.
是的，当然。我上星期刚见过它。
Even if you did believe me...
即使你相信我...
I doubt if there
is anything you could do.
我也怀疑你是否能去做些什么。
I've already gone
to the State Department...
我已经去过国务院...
and they will do nothing...
并且他们什么也不会去做...
but I had to let you know.
但我必须让你知道。
Good-bye, Mr. Braddock.
再见，巴洛克先生。
God be with you.
上帝与你同在。
Braddock?
巴洛克？
C.I.A.
中央情报局
Please come with us.
请跟我们来。
Wait outside.
在外面等着。
It's been a long time,
Colonel Braddock.
很久不见了，巴洛克上校。
How have you been?
你过得如何？
You know how I've
been, Littlejohn.
你知道我过得怎么样，小约翰。
Now, what do you want?
现在，你想要什么？
You just met with
a Reverend Polanski.
你刚刚会见了一个叫波兰斯基的牧师。
So?
如何？
Did he tell you
some kind of...
他有没有告诉你那种...
crazy story about
your wife being alive?
关于你妻子还活着的疯狂故事？
Is it a crazy story?
这是一个疯狂的故事？
Of course it is.
当然是。
Big mistake, Littlejohn.
大错误，小约翰。
I didn't believe it until now.
直到现在我都无法相信这件事。
What are you going to do
about getting them out?
为了救他们出来，你将会怎么做？
Nothing.
什么都不做。
If I don't get them out...
如果我不把他们救出来...
they're going to die.
他们将会死去。
People die every day.
每天都有人死亡。
Braddock!
巴洛克！
I'm warning you.
我警告你。
Don't step on any toes.
别踩到任何脚趾。【别得罪任何人。】
I don't step on toes,
Littlejohn.
我不会踩到脚趾,小约翰。
I step on necks.
我踩到脖子上。
【不仅得罪，还要惩罚。】
Welcome to Bangkok.
欢迎来到曼谷。【泰国首都】
We hope you enjoyed
your flight...
我们希望您享受这次飞行之旅...
and will fly
with Thai Airlines again.
并再次乘坐泰国航空公司的飞机。
Take me downtown.
带我去市中心。
40 bob, please.
请支付40块。
Now, look here, mate.
现在，看这里，伴侣。
I said I need more room.
我说过我需要更多房间。
Now beat it!
现在打它！
Whoo! You take me home.
呼！你带我回家。
You want to try knocking me off?
你想试试击倒我吗？
How the hell are you, Braddock?
你怎么样，巴洛克？
Did you get everything?
你一切都准备好了吗？
Yes, I got everything...
是的，一切都有了...
but it sure as hell wasn't easy.
但肯定是非常不容易。
That's why
I appreciate you, Mik.
这就是我欣赏你的原因，米克。
That's what friends
are for, Braddock...
这就是朋友的作用，巴洛克...
which reminds me.
我想起来了。
Got my money?
我的钱带来了吗？
Let's go.
我们走。
No, no, no!
No need to hurry.
不，不，不！不要急。
The plane won't be loaded
for several hours yet.
几个小时之内飞机还不会降落。
We got a long drive out of town.
我们需要很长一段驾驶开出城市。
Oh, shit. Here comes trouble.
哦，见鬼。麻烦来了。
Go get the car
and pull out front.
去把汽车开到前面来。
Ah, OK.
啊，好的。
Hey.
嘿。
You're not going
anywhere, Miklachek.
你不能去任何地方，米克拉查克。
Take him to the car.
把他带到汽车那边。
Jeez. Hey, where's
the rules about...
老天。嘿，这是依据什么规则...
Hey, watch my beer,
man! Hey, listen.
嘿，小心我的啤酒，老兄！嘿，听着。
I warned you, Braddock,
not to fuck with us.
我警告你，巴洛克，别逼我们。
Don't try to stop me,
Littlejohn.
不要尝试阻止我，小约翰。
You're stopped.
你被阻止了。
Come on.
来吧。
Oh! Oh, my God!
哦！哦，我的天！
Freeze, asshole,
or you're dead!
住手，混蛋，否则你死定了！
Excuse me, girls.
对不起，姑娘们。
Braddock!
巴洛克！
Cut him off!
拦下他！
Braddock!
巴洛克！
Braddock.
巴洛克。
Stop right there.
站在那别动！
Braddock! Wait!
巴洛克！等等！
Son of a bitch.
婊子养的。【王八蛋】
You actually made it.
你真的成功了。
- Shit! - Uh -oh.
- 娘的！-额 -哦。
Braddock!
He's getting away!
巴洛克！他正在逃离！
Hurry! Get in your cars!
Go after him! Hit it!
快点！进你们的车！跟着他！打它！
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Way to go, man!
做得好，伙计！
【That's the way to go. 的缩写，用来告诉一个人"他做得很好，请继续保持"。】
Jesus, Braddock.
天啊【耶稣】，巴洛克。
Couldn't you lighten up
just a teeny bit?
你就不能放松一点点？
I mean, I got to live here.
我的意思是，我住在这里。
You've got a one-way
ticket out.
你已经有出去的单程票了。
Jesus, Braddock.
天啊，巴洛克。
Watch it!
小心！
Whoa!
哇哦！
Oh, shit, Braddock.
哦，见鬼，巴洛克。
We'll have the whole
damn police force after us.
我们会招来整个该死的警察局跟着。
How far is it
to the plane?
到飞机还有多远？
Uh, it's quite a ways
out of Bangkok.
额，出了曼谷还有相当一段路。
No. It will be daylight
before we get there.
不。在我们到达之前就会天亮。
Hey, the boss is coming!
嘿，老板来了！
Don't hang around!
别整天闲逛！
Why didn't you have
her going, man?
你们为什么不启动她，伙计？
Let's go!
出发！
Come, come, come!
来吧，来吧，来吧！
Are you sure this thing
will get off the ground?
你确定这东西能飞上天？
Oh, relax, mother.
哦，放松，老妈。
Sit back. Enjoy the ride.
坐后面去。享受这次航行。
It'll be just like Coney Island.
它将和康尼岛一样。
OK, Braddock...
好吧，巴洛克...
are you gonna tell me
where we're going now?
你现在想告诉我 我们要去哪里了吗？
As if I didn't know.
我好像不知道。
Along the coast.
Ganh Rai Bay.
沿着海岸。争莱湾。【西贡河出口】
We're gonna have to
skim the waves...
看来我们必须掠过波浪...
when we get there to
stay underneath their radar.
当我们到达那里就要保持在他们的雷达下面。
Hey, Braddock, you've
done some flying.
嘿，巴洛克，你已经做过一些飞行了。
Why don't you take
the controls, eh?
你为什么不来控制，额？
Give me a rest.
让我休息一下。
Let's see if you can fly
as well as you can drive, eh?
让我们瞧瞧你的飞行技术是否和你的驾车技术一样好，额？
It's been a long time.
已经有一段时间了。
Oh, you can do it.
哦，你可以做到的。
I tell you...
我会告诉你...
it's a lot calmer up here...
在这里平静的多...
than it is in your automobile.
比起在你的汽车里。
You know, when we get
to the drop zone...
你知道，当我们到达降落区...
I'm gonna pull her
up into a climb...
我将会拉起她变成爬坡...
and you'll have
about five seconds...
并且你只有5秒钟...
to make the drop before
I put her into a dive.
在我把她变成俯冲之前来完成降落。
I'll need ten seconds.
我需要10秒钟。
Well, if you're a good boy,
I'll give you ten seconds.
好吧，如果你是个好男孩，我会给你10秒钟。
Vietnam.
越南。
I never thought
I'd be coming back.
我从没想过还会再回来。
I guess we never really
can leave, can we?
我想我们从未真正能离开，能吗？
Aw, come on.
嗷，加油。
Get your ass back there.
到后面去。
I'll take it.
我要执行了。
OK, Braddock.
好吧，巴洛克。
You got thirty seconds.
你有30秒。
Good luck, mother.
好运，老妈。
See you in hell,
you crazy bastard.
地狱里见，你这疯狂的混蛋。
Come on!
来吧！
Let us each give thanks
in our own way.
让我们各自用自己的方式来感恩。
- Amen. - Amen.
- 阿门。-阿门。
Thank you, Father,
wise and good...
谢谢你，上帝，聪明又善良...
for home and friends
and daily food.
为了家庭、朋友们和日常的食物。
Bless, dear Lord,
the food we take...
保佑，亲爱的主，我们吃的食物...
and keep us all...
并让我们所有人...
Oh, my God.
哦，我的上帝。
And keep us all home and safe.
并让我们所有人安全回家。
Amen.
阿门。
Please start without me.
请你们先开始吃吧。
I'll be right back.
我马上会回来。
Braddock.
巴洛克。
How on earth did you get here?
你到底是怎么到这里来的?
Where's my wife?
我的妻子在哪儿？
She doesn't live very far.
她住得并不是很远。
Can you tell me
how to get there?
你能告诉我怎么到那儿吗？
I'll take you there.
我会带你去那儿。
Here. Wear this.
There's a curfew.
这里。戴上这顶。那边有一个宵禁。
We must be very careful.
我们必须非常小心。
I tried to tell you
how bad it was.
我尝试着告诉你那里有多恶劣。
You'd better go, Reverend.
你最好还是离开，牧师。
And thanks.
谢谢。
Good luck. God bless you.
祝你好运。上帝保佑你。
I didn't know.
我并不知道。
I thought you were...
我以为你已经...
It's not important.
这并不重要。
I prayed you would
come for us...
我祈祷着你会为我们而来...
and you are here.
然后你到这里了。
That is all that matters
to Van and I.
这对凡和我来说才是最重要的。
This is your son, Jim.
这是你的儿子，吉姆。
Hello, Van.
你好，凡。
I speak English, Braddock.
我会说英语，巴洛克。
For years, he dreamed about you.
多年来，他都梦到你。
Sometimes, in very
difficult moments...
有时候，在非常艰难的时刻...
I would find him
talking to you...
我会找到他谈论你...
as if you were there...
好像你就在那里...
and somehow you would
make things right for him...
并且不论如何你都是做了对他有利的事情...
but one day,
he stopped believing.
但是有一天，他不再相信。
I tried to keep you
alive in his heart.
我尝试着让你活在他的心里。
I tried.
我试过了。
I guess I know
how you feel, Van...
我想我知道你的感受，凡...
thinking that I deserted
you and your mother...
认为是我抛弃了你和你的妈妈...
but... I want you
to know that...
但是...我想让你知道...
Van, please.
凡，拜托。
If I had known that you
and your mother were alive...
如果我早就知道你和你妈妈还活着...
there's nothing in the world...
那么世界上就没有什么...
that would have stopped me
from coming for you before now.
可以在此之前阻止我为你而来。
You've suffered so much.
你已经受了那么多苦。
I know I have changed, Jim.
我知道我已经变了，吉姆。
I'm sorry I'm no longer
pretty for you.
很遗憾，对你来说我已经不再漂亮。
You'll always be
beautiful to me.
对我而言你永远是最美丽的。
We have to go now.
我们现在必须离开。
We are ready.
我们都准备好了。
Let me check the street first.
先让我查看一下街道。
Van, hurry.
凡，快点。
Come on.
来吧。
Hurry, hurry.
快点，快点。
The boat's right down there.
汽船就在那下面。
It might be a tight squeeze...
也许会有点拥挤...
but I think you're going
to enjoy the ride, Van.
但我认为你已经准备好享受航行了，凡。
If you say so, Braddock.
如果你说是，那就是吧，巴洛克。
Please be patient.
请耐心点。
We've only had each other
for twelve years...
我们相依为命12年了...
and now...
现在...
it is very difficult for him.
对他而言很艰难。
He will need some time.
他需要一些时间。
We have all the time
in the world.
我们拥有世上的所有时间。
I love you very much,
Jim Braddock.
我非常爱你，詹姆斯・巴洛克。
I think I should talk
to our son for a moment.
我认为我应该和我们儿子谈一会儿。
I'll go get the boat ready.
我去把船准备好。
Van.
凡。
Everything will be all right.
一切都会好起来的。
You don't care about me now.
你现在不关心我了。
You only care about HIM.
你只关心他！
That is not true.
不是这样的。
It was our love that
brought you into this world.
是我们的爱情让你诞生在这个世界上。
Your father loves you as I do.
你父亲和我一样爱你。
If you will only
give him a chance.
只要你给他一次机会。
Please try, Van.
请尝试去做，凡。
I'm very scared.
我很害怕。
I know you are...
我都知道...
but once we get to America...
但是一旦我们到了美国...
everything will be better.
一切都会变得更好。
I promise.
我发誓。
Your father promises.
你爸爸也发誓。
Lin, we have to
get out of here.
林，我们必须离开这里。
Hurry!
赶快！
Foolish.
愚蠢。
You're in Nam.
你在越南。
Very foolish to come back.
回来是相当愚蠢的。
I am General Quoc.
我是阔克将军。
How do you do, Madam Braddock?
你过得怎么样，巴洛克夫人？
And yoi.
你呢。
And this must be your son Van.
这一定是你的儿子凡。
Very good-looking boy.
很帅气的男孩。
When I received the report...
当我收到报告...
that a strange-looking boat
had outrun my gunboats...
一艘外形奇特的船已经逃过我的炮艇...
and heading towards
Ho Chi Minh city...
并朝着胡志明市而去...
I took the privilege...
我假设...
of assuming it was you,
Colonel Braddock...
那是你的特权,巴洛克上校...
since Reverend Polanski
had just returned...
因为波兰斯基牧师刚刚返回...
from your country...
自你们国家...
but now...
但是现在...
Braddock...
巴洛克...
you must pay for the crimes
that you have committed...
你必须就致力于反对我所热爱的国家...
against my beloved country.
而犯下的罪行付出代价。
They have nothing
to do with this.
他们与此无关。
You are absolutely right.
你绝对地正确。
No!
不！
Ma!
妈！
You will find your first test...
你会发现 你第一项测试...
quite challenging.
相当具有挑战性。
Usually, we use people
who are...
通常，我们使用的人会...
a little bit taller.
更高一点。
I have tested
many before, Braddock...
我之前已经测试过很多了，巴洛克...
and no one has lasted
even an hour.
并且没有人能坚持超过哪怕1个小时。
Maybe you can be the first, eh?
你也许会成为第一个，额？
I'll do whatever you want.
我会做任何你想要的。
Just let the boy go.
只要你放走那个男孩。
You will do what I want anyways.
不管怎样你都会做我想要的。
Well done.
很好。
Well done, Colonel Braddock.
非常好，巴洛克上校。
You are every bit as tough
as your reputation.
你每一点都像你的声誉一样强硬。
I like that.
我喜欢那样。
You have not disappointed
me, Braddock.
你没有让我失望，巴洛克。
No!
不！
This has gone on long enough.
这已经持续了足够长的时间。
No!
不！
Van!
凡！
I'm in here!
我在这里！
Come on! Come on!
加油！加油！
Can you make it?
你能做到吗？
Yeah.
能。
Go to the mission.
去教会。
What's wrong?
怎么回事？
What are you doing?
你们在干什么？
Where is Braddock?
巴洛克在哪里？
I don't know where
Braddock is, General.
我不知道巴洛克在哪里，将军。
You lie, priest. You lie!
你在撒谎，牧师。你在撒谎！
We know you helped Braddock!
我们知道你在帮助巴洛克！
I? You must be mistaken.
我？你肯定是弄错了。
You lie!
你在撒谎！
Perhaps a change
of environment...
或许换一个环境...
will help you
to think more clearly!
会帮你想地更清楚！
Take him!
带走他！
Please, no.
请求，别。
I can't leave my children.
我不能离开我的孩子们。
They need me!
他们需要我！
Of course!
当然！
I would not want
to separate you...
我不想把你...
from your half-breed
American bastard children!
和你的混蛋半混血美国孩子们拆开！
Take them all!
把所有人都带走！
Priest, your new home
will be Olaha prison!
牧师，殴拉哈监狱将成为你们的新家！
Don't! Don't!
不要！不要！
Don't!
不要！
No! No!
不！不！
Stop!
停下！
停！
Kids! In the truck!
孩子们！上卡车！
Van!
凡！
Where's the Reverend?
牧师在哪里？
I know! I get him, Braddock!
我知道！我去找他，巴洛克！
Come on, Reverend.
加油，牧师。
Thank God, Braddock!
感谢上帝，巴洛克！
Protect yourself!
保护好你们自己！
Reverend, get the kids
out of here!
牧师，把孩子们从这里弄出去！
Out! Hurry! Hurry!
出去！快点！快点！
We must get away
from the truck!
我们必须远离卡车！
Hurry up, Braddock! Here!
快点，巴洛克！这边！
Get down, Reverend!
趴下，牧师！
It's OK.
没事了。
Ninety kilometers to the border.
距离边境90公里。
You don't expect
these children...
你不是期望这些孩子们...
to walk ninety kilometers!
步行90公里吧！
I don't expect
a damn thing, Reverend.
我不期望一件该死的事情，牧师。
But walk or crawl,
we're gonna make it.
但是不管走还是爬，我们必须做到。
Come on, kids.
加油，孩子们。
Come on, Reverend.
加油，牧师。
Braddock...
巴洛克...
the children are dead tired.
孩子们累得要命。
We must stop to rest.
你必须停下来休息。
Please, Braddock.
拜托，巴洛克。
They are not very strong.
他们不是很强壮。
Wait here.
在这里等着。
Reverend. Reverend!
牧师。牧师！
Bring the kids.
把孩子们带来。
Hurry.
赶快。
Come. Come, children.
来吧。来，孩子们。
Quiet. Be quiet.
安静。保持安静。
Come, children. Hurry. Hurry.
来，孩子们。快。快。
Come, children.
来吧，孩子们。
Be careful. Be careful.
Don't hurt yourselves.
小心。小心。别伤着自己。
Come.
来。
Go. Go.
走。走。
Come on, kids. Hurry!
加油，孩子们。快点！
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry up!
快点！快点！赶快！
Thomas!
托马斯！
Hurry!
快点！
Sit down and hold on.
坐下，抓稳。
Damn it.
该死的。
Braddock, get back, you bastard!
巴洛克，回来，你这个杂种！
Come on!
来吧！
Hold on!
抓稳！
Braddock! I will kill you...
巴洛克！我会杀了你...
and I will burn
those filthy children!
还会烧死那些肮脏的孩子们！
Hold on.
抓稳。
Oh, my God.
哦，我的上帝。
Get back there
with the kids, Reverend.
回到孩子们中去，牧师。
It's gonna get rough.
马上要变艰难。
It's going to get rough.
正在变地艰难。
Mayday. Mayday.
呼救。呼救。
This is
Colonel James Braddock...
这里是巴洛克上校...
calling American Military
Assistance Command.
呼叫美国军事援助指挥部。
Come in.
进来。
Mayday. Mayday.
呼救。呼救。
Here. Take a seat.
这里，坐下。
Mayday. Mayday.
呼救。呼救。
This is Colonel Braddock.
这里是巴洛克上校。
I'm in a crippled C-47.
我在一架受损的C-47上。
I have a planeload
of Amerasian children.
我有整整一飞机的美亚混血儿童。
Losing fuel.
正在漏油。
I'm approximately eight miles
east of the Thai border.
我大约在泰国边境以东8英里处。【1英里=1.6公里】
If anyone can hear me,
please transfer this message...
如果任何人能听到我，请把这条信息转发...
to the American Military
Assistance Command.
给美国军事援助指挥部。
Is everyone OK back there?
那边每个人都还好吗？
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
Yeah. I fine.
是的。我很好。
How you?
你怎样？
I'm fine, too.
我也很好。
Reverend! We're going down!
牧师！我们在坠落！
Children! Get down!
孩子们！趴下！
Hold on! Hold on!
坚持住！坚持住！
We're gonna die!
我们会死！
Just hold on!
只要坚持住！
Van.
凡。
Come on, Van.
来吧，凡。
Help the kids.
帮助孩子们。
Everybody down.
全都趴下。
Reverend.
牧师。
My God.
我的上帝！
Braddock, there's the border.
巴洛克，那边就是边境。
As soon as I take
the guards out...
一旦我除去守卫们...
you get the kids
over the bridge...
你就带孩子们过桥...
as fast as you can.
越快越好。
Did you hear what I said?
你听到我说的了吗？
On my way over here...
来这里的路上...
I was wondering
what you would be like.
我很疑惑你会是什么样子。
I want you to know...
我想让你知道...
you're everything
I wanted in a son...
你是我期待的那个好儿子...
and I'm very proud of you.
我为你感到非常骄傲。
I love you.
我爱你。
All right, men. Let's go.
好了，伙计们。出发。
What the hell is happening, Dan?
那边正在发生什么鬼事情，丹？
Braddock and the children.
巴洛克和孩子们。
We intercepted a radio message.
我们收到一条无线电信息。
They crashed
somewhere near here.
他们在这附近坠机。
Oh, shit.
哦，见鬼。
Van!
凡！
Don't go!
别去！
Can't leave him, Dan.
不能离开他，丹。
I got to help him.
我要去帮他。
Leave it alone, General.
He's on his own.
让他一个人战斗，将军。他只能靠自己。
No one crosses the border.
没人可以穿越边境。
Get a medic in, man.
找一个医生进去，伙计。
All right!
好的！
Daddy!
爸爸！
Don't go!
别过去！
Christ.
老天。【基督】
I got you, Braddock!
我逮到你了，巴洛克！
I got you!
我逮到你了！
Daddy!
爸爸！
No, no. No, Van.
Get back! Get back!
不，不。不，凡。退后！退后！
No. No. Please!
不。不。拜托！
You're finished, Braddock!
你完蛋了，巴洛克！
I've won!
我赢了！
They will not dare to cross.
他们不敢穿越。
What's he doing?
他在干什么？
Hold your position.
保持你的位置.
He makes one wrong move,we'll climb up his ass.
只要他的一个错误举动，我们就会爬上他的屁股。【炸了他】
You got it.
你说得对。
The Americans are bluffing.
美国人在吓唬人。
They will not dare do any more.
他们不敢再做了。
Fire! Fire!
开火！开火！
Dad!
爸爸！
There he is!
他在那儿！
Oh, Braddock.
哦，巴洛克。
Thank God you are alive.
感谢上帝你还活着。
Come on, children.
加油，孩子们。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Bless you.
保佑你。
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
英文字幕从www.AllSubs.org下载
新浪微博@蓝色风暴911 原创翻译